Mom, why are you leaving in such a hurry?
Why not stay a few more days?
Your dad is home alone.
You know how he is.
He definitely won't
eat properly without me.
I'll definitely go back
to visit you next month.
Qingqing,
I need to apologize to you.
I got the wrong person before.
What are you talking about?
There's no need to apologize.
Don't worry.
We've already
handed it over to the police.
When you were little,
I just wanted you
to study hard and get good grades.
When you grew up, I wanted you
to work hard
and get a job at a big company.
You didn't let us down.
You're my good daughter.
It's just...
I feel like I'm not a good mother.
I always wanted
you to find a well-off man,
but I don't know
if that's what you wanted.
That's not true.
You're the best mom in the world.
I just want my daughter
to be happy forever.
No matter what you do,
your dad and I will always support you.
Don't cry.
Mom feels that Shen really likes you.
Mom and Dad just want you to find someone
who truly likes and cherishes you.
Look at you, crying like a little kitten.
Stop crying.
There, there. Don't cry.
Not sleeping in the middle of the night,
doing a puzzle all by yourself?
What a beautiful aurora.
A gift from Shen Feng?
Have you found the answer?
Maybe.
What do you mean, maybe?
Love is love.
If you don't love him, you don't.
There's no middle ground in love.
When I first met Zhang Yi,
from our ups and downs
to talking about marriage,
I thought I had love and happiness.
But in the end, I found out that
what I was holding tightly
wasn't chocolate,
but dog shit.
I did fall for Shen Feng,
but I'm not sure
if this relationship is chocolate.
You don't trust Shen Feng?
No, Shen Feng is great.
He's someone I can trust and rely on.
I just don't trust myself.
Do I still have the energy
to maintain a relationship?
Can I still love?
I'm afraid of disappointing Shen Feng
and myself.
Why would you think that?
You have to believe that you are the best.
Whoever is with you
will be happy.
Don't just blame yourself
when you run into problems.
Think more about other people's faults.
People get lost
because they think too much
and do too little.
Thinking only brings problems.
You only find the answers by doing.
Don't miss out
on an entire orchard
just because of one bad fruit.
You should ask it
if it really wants it.
Be more determined.
Shout out
what you really want!
I want Shen Feng.
His body, his soul,
I want everything about him.
I want it all.
You imitate that so well.
Brother, where did
these flowers come from?
They're beautiful.
Huohuo, do you like Qingqing?
How about I make Qingqing
a part of our family?
I do, but I'm still too young.
She'll have to wait for me.
I'll grow up fast and marry her.
In your dreams.
Look at you, getting all defensive.
I've always known you like Qingqing.
Go for it.
I'm rooting for you.
Qingqing,
Shen Feng,
I've decided on my wish.
What is it?
I want to see you
right now.
Wasn't that my wish before?
That's right,
but now it's mine.
I'll wait for you at the usual place.
Come on, brother!
Shen Feng,
I have something to tell you.
Me too.
You... I...
Let me go first.
Okay.
I know you're hesitating and struggling,
but I really hope
you can give me another chance
to prove that
I love you.
You just said everything I wanted to say.
Take it back. Take it back.
You can
say it again.
But I only want to hear
the last three words.
Three words?
Can you stop being so weird?
I'm literally dying of nervousness,
and you...
Hello.
Are you here to check in?
I'm the manager.
Qingqing.
Tangtang.
My Qingqing.
My financing completely failed.
Wall Street doesn't appreciate me.
What should I do?
I'm going to be blacklisted.
Don't panic.
Come, sit down and tell me.
Business at Yunbianshang
has been great lately.
We held an event recently
and attracted a lot of guests.
They all gave us good reviews.
It won't be long
before we're out of debt
and making a profit.
No, the B&B's profits are too unstable.
I'm tired. I'm exhausted.
I really can't hold on anymore.
I'm going to sell it right now.
Maybe I can get some money
to pay off my debts.
Do you have to sell it?
Yes, I'm selling it right now.
Okay, then just sell it to me.
Stop joking.
What are you talking about?
Where would you get that kind of money?
The wedding fund I saved up.
I don't need it anymore.
I might as well use it all.
If it's not enough,
I'll figure out the rest.
I'll cover the rest.
Hold on.
Shen Feng,
the top student.
No.
Y-You guys are...
Tang,
I'll tell you all the gossip
in detail later.
Shen Feng, don't do anything rash.
Who's being impulsive?
What? Am I supposed to
just watch you make money?
I've been jealous for a long time.
The previous collab between
Yunbianshang and the tea garden
was a huge success.
Everyone says we're a package deal.
Let's just take it over together.
You'll be the major shareholder,
and I'll be the second. How about that?
Really?
Of course.
Let's sign the contract right now.
Sign the contract right now.
When I first lost my job,
I thought about ending it all.
But Shen Feng was actually right.
What I wanted to end wasn't my life,
but the pain.
Smile, you two new bosses.
Change your pose. Let's take another one.
When I was at my lowest
and most frustrated,
you reached out and held me.
You made me realize
that there's never just one way to live,
and certainly not just one answer to life.
Congratulations to me.
I not only found the life I wanted,
but also the love I want to hold on to.
Actually, we don't need
to deliberately seek happiness.
As long as we avoid all pain
within our ability,
and don't let ourselves
suffer even a little bit,
don't do things we don't like,
don't associate with people we don't like,
and don't listen to words we don't like,
that is a kind of happiness.
The light came, and the rain came.
Pushing open the small door,
I saw a new world.
We live for 30,000 days,
and every day passed is one day less.
Every tomorrow is a blind box.
Who says
today can't be a hidden surprise?
Hello, I'd like to check in.
Hello, welcome.